## **BRYAN TOBIN**

## 310.848.7511, twinnis22@gmail.com

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

20 years of experience in the Information Technology field. Dedicated hardworking individual that listen to end-users to find a resolution to the problem. Familiar with VOIP systems and networking technologies. Motivator and a team builder. Works well individually or as a team. Successful in meeting new technical challenges and finding solutions to meet the needs of the client.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Support Analyst | Katten Muchin Rosenman LLP | Los Angeles, CA (REHIRE)

March 2018 - June 2018

April 2019 - Present

- Receive requests via telephone, voice mail, e-mail, or in-person from Firm employees and/or clients for computer technical assistance.
- Collect and log detailed information to categorize requests to determine method of resolution.
- Analyze problems (1) attempt hardware/software solution by telephone, email, or by providing floor support; or (2)
  decide proper level to escalate calls to technical support staff for hardware, network, or other problems that cannot
  be resolved.
- Provides technical assistance for remote users Virtual Desktop, Citrix/Xen, Web Applications and Cisco VPN.
- Support and setup audio-video equipment in conference rooms.
- Recognize, troubleshoot, and diagnose computer, phone, printer, software, and network connectivity problems.
- Conduct new-hire training (attorney, legal executive/administrative assistant, paralegal, and administrative) in individual and classroom style settings.
- Conduct one-on-one attorney training sessions, with emphasis on PDA's, laptops, and remote computing issues.

Environment: Windows 10, Office 2016 / 365, Android & iPhone, Active Directory, Service Now, Video conference setups.

#### 

- Respond to requests for technical assistance in person via phone, and electronically.
- Diagnose and resolve technical hardware, software, VoIP phone, and smartphone issues.
- On-site representative and contact for technology vendor appointments.
- Setup, testing, and delivery of meetings and conferences within the office.
- Track, route, and redirect problems to correct resources.
- Log all help desk interactions in the ticketing system.
- Follow up with customers, provide feedback, and see problems through to resolution, including escalated calls.
- Ensure proper recording, documentation, and closure of all end user help calls or requests.
- Prepare videoconference and A/V equipment for meetings and troubleshoot connectivity issues, if needed.

Environment: Windows 10, Office 2016 / 365, Android & iPhone, Active Directory, Service Now, Video conference setup

### Technical Support Supervisor | Jenner & Block | Los Angeles, CA

- Responsible for the day-to-day IT operation of the LA office (approximately 100 end users), and supervision of the Systems Support Specialist.
- Monitor daily workflow and work assignments; act as a liaison for all Audio Visual related activities, including set-up, troubleshooting and repair of Audio Visual equipment.
- Perform performance evaluations of Systems Support Specialist.
- Maintain the call tracking system through the input of resolutions to issues and track issues that are escalated; enter data and add or delete information accurately and timely into the call tracking system.
- Add remove end user accounts in AD / configure email accounts US MS Exchange.
- Setup and configured MACs, installed software, created and deleted user accounts.
- Telecom Admin configured, add and delete telecom line and voicemail accounts.
- Maintain an inventory of all technology equipment (computers, hand-held devices, monitors, printers).
- Setup and configure video conferencing equipment.

Environment: Windows 10 & MAC, Office 2016 / 365, Android & iPhone, Active Directory, Service Now, Video conference setup

# Computer Hardware/telecommunications Technician II | Venable LLP | Los Angeles, CA

November 2013 - February 2017

- Responsible for the installation and configuration of computer hardware and serving as an escalation point to the
  Service Desk staff in troubleshooting and resolving PC hardware problems; Hardware includes desktop hardware,
  printers, wiring/wiring centers and other devices connected to the firm's network; Responsible for processing,
  responding and troubleshooting day-to-day telecommunication and mobile device issues/problems; and
  coordinating, updating and maintaining the firm equipment assets in accordance with established policies and
  procedures.
- Program Cisco Call Manager, voice mail.
- Maintain and track inventory of office telephone equipment for all firm offices; install and configure mobile devices
- Assist with roll out of new hardware and provide training to users.
- Maintain confidentiality regarding firm/client matters.
- Monitor service desk tickets and assign to appropriate group.
- Support San Francisco office bi-weekly visits.
- Train other IT staff on policies and procedures.
- Setup and maintain video conference equipment.

Environment: Windows 10, Office 2016 / 365, Android & iPhone, Active Directory, Service Now, Video conference setup

## IT Manager | McDermott, Will & Emery LLP | Los Angeles, CA

January 1997 - March 2013

- Supervised a staff.
- Implemented help desk solutions.
- Installed, supported, and administered a network of 200 end users.
- Prepared and presented reports as necessary to the Office Administrator.
- Consulted with attorneys and staff on project requirements or for problem resolution.
- Researched, evaluated, and recommended new technologies and products that would benefit the overall network environment.
- Administered desktop upgrades, repairs, service packs, and hot fixes.

- Supported Microsoft Office Suite, network printing environment, and Lotus Notes Mail configuration.
- Implemented desktop upgrades from Windows 98 to Windows XP Professional, Win 7; and from Office 2000 to Office XP Professional to Office 2003 Professional.
- Performed user access maintenance, including creation and deletion of user accounts in Microsoft Active Directory.
- Developed solutions, designs, and specifications to satisfy user needs.
- Followed up with users to ensure satisfaction with services provided.
- Created and documented Help Desk policies, procedures, and processes.
- Logged all customer problem calls and e-mails, documented desk-side support, and updated status information into the Help Desk database software.
- Configure and troubleshoot iPhone, iPad, Blackberry, and Android devices Telephony & Networking: Avaya Integrated Management, Audix and Cisco Call Manager Operating Systems: Windows HP SERVER, APC UPS System, and various switch configurations.
- Protocols: TCP/IP, FTP and TFTP Certifications: A+ and Network.

Environment: Windows XP & 7, Office 2012, Blackberry, Android & iPhone, Active Directory, Video conference setup, Telcom phone & voicemail setups.

IC3 - Interior Communications Electrician | United States Navy | Norfolk, VA

August 1992 - August 1996

## **EDUCATION**

HS Diploma June 1991

Manual Arts Senior High School, Los Angeles, CA